An epic of epic epicness.
Scott Pilgrim vs. the World is a action, comedy,
romance film directed by Edgar Wright.
As bass guitarist for a garage-rock band, Scott Pilgrim has never had trouble
getting a girlfriend; usually, the problem is getting rid of them.
But when Ramona Flowers skates into his heart, he finds she has the most troublesome baggage of all: an
army of ex-boyfriends who will stop at nothing to eliminate him from her list of suitors.
Scott Pilgrim, played by Michael Cera.
Ramona Flowers, played by Mary Elizabeth Winstead.
Knives Chau, played by Ellen Wong.
Wallace Wells, played by Kieran Culkin.
Kim Pine, played by Alison Pill.
Stephen Stills, played by Mark Webber.
Scott Pilgrim vs.
The World: The Game is a side-scrolling beat 'em up game developed by Ubisoft Montreal and Ubisoft Chengdu and published by Ubisoft, based on the
Scott Pilgrim series of Oni Press graphic novels by Bryan Lee O'Malley and tying in with the release of the film of the same name.
The game was originally released digitally for Xbox 360 via Xbox Live Arcade and PlayStation 3
via PlayStation Network in August 2010 before being delisted in December 2014.
An updated re-release for Nintendo Switch, PlayStation 4, Windows,
Xbox One and Google Stadia titled Scott Pilgrim vs.
The World: The Game – Complete Edition, was released on January 14, 2021.
The film explores themes of video game, skateboarding,
ex-boyfriend, ex-girlfriend, toronto, canada.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.